salvex.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy | Salvex

This Privacy Policy Statement describes the privacy practices of Salvex, Inc., (the "Company" or "we") with respect to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information, including in respect to information collected from individuals or entities listing products for sale or bidding for the purchase of Products on the Company's website located at http://salvex.com/ ("Salvex Website") or otherwise accessing or utilizing the Salvex Website ("Users"). This Privacy Policy Statement is part of Salvex Web Site Terms and Conditions. This Privacy Policy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between the Company and an User from time to time.

Where we have provided a translation of the English language version of this Privacy Statement, such translation is provided for Users’ convenience only. To the extent there is any inconsistency between the English language version of this Privacy Statement and any such translation, the English language version shall govern.

In this Privacy Policy Statement, "personal information" means any information about an identifiable User, excluding any information that has been made anonymous or that is excluded from the definition of "personal information" under applicable laws.

This Privacy Policy Statement will notify Users of:

  * What personal information or third party personal information is collected through Salvex Website
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to Users regarding collection, use and distribution of personal information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under our control
  * How Users can correct any inaccuracies in their personal information

### Information Collection

Except where otherwise required or permitted by law, we will inform Users of the purposes for the collection, use, or disclosure of the Users’ personal information prior to collecting, using or disclosing the personal information. We collect personal information from Users through various means, including through Salvex Website and through user registration. Requirements for consent to collection, use, or disclosure of personal information vary depending on circumstances and on the type of personal information that is intended to be collected, used, or disclosed. In determining whether consent is required and, if so, which form of consent is appropriate, we will take into account both the sensitivity of the personal information at issue and the purposes for which we will use the information. Consent may be express, implied (including through use of "opt-out" consent where appropriate), or deemed. For example, if a User provides his/her/its mailing address and requests information regarding a particular Product, consent to use the address to mail product information to the User is implied. On giving reasonable written notice to the Company, a User may withdraw consent to the collection, use, or disclosure of his/her/its personal information. Upon receipt of this withdrawal, we will notify the User of the likely consequences of withdrawing his/her/its consent. Except where otherwise required or permitted by law, the company will then stop collecting, using or disclosing the User’s personal information.

### Information Use

We use information collected from Users to provide Products or services (including disclosure of personal information to third parties as required to provide those Products or services, and as described herein), to respond to requests for information regarding the Company’s Products and services, and for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. The information gathered will be used for general corporate marketing purposes, thereby enabling us to refine and improve our service and better meet our customers' needs. The information gathered may also be used by the Company to resolve disputes, collect fees, troubleshoot problems, enforce our Salvex Web Site Terms and Conditions and related policies, and prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities. We will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the User or as required or permitted by law. Once the information is no longer required to fulfill its intended purposes, and is no longer required or permitted to be retained for legal or business purposes, it will be destroyed, erased, or made anonymous.

### Information Disclosure

We are the sole owner of the information collected on this site and will not share or rent this information to others in any way other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy Statement. By using the Salvex Website to buy or sell, Users consent to our disclosing relevant contact information of Sellers and Buyers to each other to the extent necessary to perform Salvex’s services in connection with a Listing Description (or in some cases, Salvex services requested by User and provided that are unrelated to a Salvex AuctionTM or Listed Description), or in the event of a dispute between the parties. We may disclose certain personal information to third parties and to affiliated entities in order to carry out work on behalf of the Company or in connection with the operation of affiliated or hosted marketplace venues. We will take appropriate steps to ensure that such recipients safeguard the personal information and use the information only for authorized purposes. If we partner with another party to provide specific services, and a User registers for these services, we will share the contact information or other information necessary for the third party to provide the requested services. We may also disclose personal information to legal, financial, and other professional advisors and to our lenders or insurers in connection with the operation of our business, or in connection with the sale or reorganization of all or part of our business or operations. In respect of our fraud detection and prevention efforts or the investigation of unlawful activities, we may collect and disclose personal information in cooperation with law enforcement authorities. We may also collect and provide personal information to other third parties in response to a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, or when we in good faith believe disclosure is required by any applicable law, regulation or legal process. By using the Salvex Website, Users agree to allow us to use Users’ remarks, suggestions, writings or comments as we so determine without Users’ further consent and without compensation or any other interests or rights. However, we will not identify the specific source of the comments by name or email address without your permission. Users also agree that we will not be liable for use or acquisition of Users’ information by any third party without our knowledge or consent.

### Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and affiliates. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual User.

### User Registration

To use certain areas of Salvex Website, Users must first register and accept Salvex Web Site Terms and Conditions. By accepting Salvex Web Site Terms and Conditions, Users expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of their personal information as described in this Privacy Statement, and in particular, after Users accept Salvex Web Site Terms and Conditions, Users expressly consent to our collecting and storing the following personal information:

  * e-mail address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * transactional information based on Users’ activities on Salvex Website (such as buying and selling), and correspondence sent to us in connection with these activities;
  * if Users are a Seller, we collect information relating to the Products Users desire to post for sale and related identifying information; and
  * other information from Users interaction with Salvex Website, or our services, content and advertising, including computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Salvex Website, IP address and standard web log information

Registration and the provision of this information are required to access some areas of Salvex Website. Users who do not input the required information will not have access to these areas.

### Special Offers, and Site and Service Updates

We may send registered Users site and service announcement updates, and information regarding new or improved services and upcoming events (including but not necessarily limited to a Salvex AuctionTM) that we think may be of interest to them. We may communicate with Users to provide requested services or with respect to their account via email or phone.

### Usage Data

The Salvex Website also collects other information through some of the features available on the site. Information including unique ID, access time, search parameters and visitor feedback is collected.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data containing information about a User and is stored on the User's hard drive. Use of a cookie is in some ways linked to personal information while on our site - see details above. The cookies have long term expirations to provide convenience to Users so that a user has to log in a password only once while on our site. If a User rejects the cookie, they will be able to use our site, but will be unable to access some areas. Cookies also enable us to track the interests of our Users, allowing us to personalize and enhance their experience on Salvex Website. We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies, and use cookies to help identify Users and maintain Users’ signed-in status. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from a User’s hard drive at the end of a session. Users are always free to decline our cookies to the extent a User’s web browser permits, although doing so may interfere with a User’s use of some of Salvex Website or services. If permitted by a User’s computer security and browser settings, we will place cookies on a User’s computer as such User browses the Salvex Website to gather non-personally identifiable information, which may include a User’s computer’s IP address, browser type, the webpage the User was visiting prior to accessing the Salvex Website, and other statistics. We use information collected from cookies so that we can understand what sort of information Users are interested in, which enables us to display advertising on your computer based on these interests. We use trusted third-party advertising companies, including without limitation Google Analytics, to serve ads when Users visit Salvex Website. These companies may use anonymized information collected through the use of cookies (not including a User’s name, address, email address, telephone number, or any other personally identifiable information) about Users’ visits to the Salvex Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to Users. This means that when Users are on websites other than the Salvex Website, Users may be shown advertising based on a User’s activity on the Salvex Website. We do not share any information with third parties that directly identifies a User.

Users can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

Users can learn more about behavioral advertising and opt out of third-party behavioral advertising by visiting [www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/).

### Web Server Traffic Log Files

Web server logs collect visitor information including IP address, browser type and version, referring URLs, referring search engines and specified search strings. This information helps us design improvements to the services and navigational structure of Salvex Website.

### Children

We do not attempt to collect personal information from children, but cannot always determine if a User of Salvex Website is a child.

### Links

The Salvex Website contains links to other sites, including sites maintained by our corporate partners for the provision of online payment services and online shipping quotes. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage Users to read the privacy statements of all websites that collect personal information.

### Surveys

Occasional surveys may be conducted on the Salvex website. Survey information will be used to help us monitor and improve the use of this site and our services.

### Management of Personal Information:

### Security

Users’ information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use a number of tools (passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect Users‘ personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other Users may abuse or misuse Users’ personal information that they collect from Salvex Website. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect Users’ privacy, we cannot ensure or warrant that Users’ personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### Choice / Opt-Out

Users are given the opportunity to “opt-out” of having their information used for purposes not directly related to the purchase of services or products using Salvex Website. Users not wanting their information provided to any companies other than the Company, or who no longer wish to receive promotional or other informational material from us may also opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the e-mail or e-mail us at info@salvex.com.

### Notification of Changes & Acceptance of Privacy Statement

By using the Salvex Website and services, Users signify their acceptance of this Privacy Policy Statement. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy Statement at any time. Users’ continued use of any portion of the Salvex Website following notification or posting of such changes will constitute a User’s acceptance of those changes. If we change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to our Privacy Policy Statement on the Salvex Website and update the date listed on the links to it, as well as on the statement itself. We will post those changes so Users are always aware of what personal information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We may from time to time provide notice of changes to this Privacy Policy Statement by email or mail, or to other contact information provided by Users. We use personal information in accordance with the Privacy Policy Statement under which the personal information was collected. If at any point, the company decides to use personal information in a manner different from what currently is stated, we will notify Users by mail, email or a phone call. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their personal information in this different manner.
